newstvplus.com 2018-05-17

# Privacy Policy | NewsTvPlus

Privacy Policy

We value the privacy policy as much as we value ours customers and visitors of the site. Newstvplus has the following privacy policy:

We will not ask you for personal information that we don’t really need but you will be required to log in to your original email while commenting and posting and giving suggestions and feed backs on the news and posts by the website.

Newstvplus  will not disclose your personal information like your email addresses to anybody, company and/or product development or to safeguard the rights of the company. The designed policy is to respect and keep private any personal information we may collect from you while you are visiting our website.

Newstvplus do not allow users to post content which are copyright and We believe and act on the “principle of News Sharing and Circulation of Information” to the users for their interest.

All the material news, events and columns on this website is will copyright or freely available and collected from different websites around the world like, facebook, twitter, different news tv channels etc.

If you find or think any News, content or article on this website is posted illegally on Newstvplus or news articles violate the copyright then you can simply send and email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Newstvplus can change the privacy policy if required and the update to the privacy policy here.

Links to Other Sites

Our website also provides links to and from leading websites like famous national and international news portals, channels and social media websites like facebook twitter dailymotion, youtube, as ZeetvPak strongly believes on the sharing and circulation of information to the users for their interest and ease.

News events and links provided from other websites are not owned or managed by us. Because we are not responsible for how these sites handle your privacy. We encourage you to check out the Privacy Policies of those other websites while visiting before giving out your personal information.

Cookies

We may collect your cookies to better you website experience. However if you do not want to enable cookies, simply adjust your browser settings before using our website and turn off cookies for Free Website Templates or our third party advertisers. Keep in mind, however, that disabling cookies may affect your user experience while visiting and exploring our website.

Third Party Ads

Advertising partners of Newstvplus may use cookies and web beacons in the ads that they serve on our website. The use of such technologies will enable the advertiser to store information about your web surfing interests, so that they can show you targeted advertisements according to your desire and interest you. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and information collected by the ads of our third party advertisers.

If you want to contact us please send your email to us

Contact

[[email protected]](http://www.newstvplus.com/contact)
